Purify and start again.
A Sacrifice is a thriller, horror film directed by Jordan Scott.
American social psychologist Ben Monroe investigates a
local cult connected to a disturbing event.
While he immerses himself into his work, his rebellious teenage daughter, Mazzy, gets involved with
a mysterious local boy, who introduces her to the city’s underground party scene.
As these two worlds head towards an intersection, Mazzy finds herself in great
danger and Ben will need to race against the clock to save her.
Ben Monroe, played by Eric Bana.
Mazzy, played by Sadie Sink.
Nina, played by Sylvia Hoeks.
Martin, played by Jonas Dassler.
Hilma, played by Sophie Rois.
Max, played by Stephan Kampwirth.
Sacrifice is a 2025 action adventure comedy film directed by Romain
Gavras, and co-written by Gavras and Will Arbery.
It stars an ensemble cast that features Anya Taylor-Joy, Chris Evans, Salma Hayek, Vincent
Cassel, Ambika Mod, Sam Richardson, Charli XCX, Yung Lean and John Malkovich.
The film had its world premiere in the Special Presentations section of the
2025 Toronto International Film Festival on  September 6, 2025.
The tone is dark and intense.